

# **ABOUT**

Junda is an Interaction Designer based in Singapore. He enjoys crafting both digital and physical experiences that serves a purpose or he is passionate about. He is passionate about the eSports industry and hopes to help prosper the industry via his designs and codes. He is currently serving his National Service, slated to end in August 2018.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

SAF 36 SCE //AUG 2016 - AUG 2018

**AES K9 DOG HANDLER** 

ONYX ISLAND //AUG 2015- OCT 2015

**DESIGN INTERN** 

SAFRA TOA PAYOH //2012 - 2016

PART TIME LIFEGUARD

OCBC Aquatic Centre | Singapore Sports Hub//2015 - 2016

PART TIME LIFEGUARD

#### **SKILLSETS**

GRAPHIC DESIGN BRANDING WEB DESIGN WEB DEVELOPMENT TYPOGRAPHY UI/UX DESIGN

ACHIEVEMENTS
NYAA SILVER // 2012
MOE EAGLES AWARD // 2012
GEEKSHACKING HACKOMANIA FIRST PLACE // 2016

# **EDUCATION**

NANYANG POLYTECHNIC//2013 - 2016

Diploma in Digital Media Design(Interaction Design)

SERANGOON GARDEN SECONDARY SCHOOL //2009 - 2012

GCE O-Level

### **LANGUAGES**

ENGLISH // Fluent CHINESE // Spoken only

#### **SOFTWARE PROFICIENCIES**

Adobe PhotoShop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Dreamweaver Brackets

HTML CSS JQUERY JAVASCRIPT ARDUINO

Bootstrap